GRADEY CULLINS

Seasoned software developer with a hunger for growth and success. Professional experience ranging from established corportate environments to disruptive startups. Client outreach, top-rated communication and the ability to be a sociable and integrated player in any work environment.

EXPERIENCE

2018 - present

Software Engineer – Hoodoo Digital Spearhead a cloud-based AEM instance managing software.

- Responsive SPA in Vue.js
- RESTful API built on Kubernetes
- Node.js CLI support

Represented Hoodoo as on-site software engineer at Western Digital to develop a pixel-perfect, mobile-first site.

- Rapid iteration cycles
- Figma mockups for precise translation

May 2017 - 2018

Full-Stack Web Developer - Navitaire

Contribute to and debug variety of internal and external enterprise software w/ 10k+ LoC.

- C# / .NET server-side software
- Development on angular SPA
- Enterprise scale MSSQL db querying, cloning, updating, etc.

EDUCATION

2013-2018

University of Utah, BS Computer Science (Expected December 2018)

- Wide diversity of CS electives
- 1st place senior capstone project
- peer-to-peer file storage system

INTERESTS

- Computer networking and SDNs
- Distributed systems and peer-to-peer software
- Cryptocurrencies
- eSports

Personal

Phone

(208) 201-7901

Email

gradeycullins@gmail.com

www

gradeycullins.com

Languages

Interpreted

- Javascript
- Python
- Shell

Compiled

- Java
- Golang
- C#

Databases

SQL

- MSSQL
- MySQL

NoSQL

mongoDB

Other

- CICD pipelines
- Automated/integration testing and deployment
- Containerization via Docker, Kubernetes
- Data science fundamentals
- Years of development in UNIX and Windows
- Modern Javascript front-end frameworks